(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-27T05:04:32.647265",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
The concert will be starting soon.
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
Attention For Visitors / Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors / Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention For Visitors
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Kikkirikiki!
Thank you all so much for coming to Takanashi Kiara
and Ninomae Ina'nis's first concert, Day 2, Drawn to Dawn!
and Ninomae Ina'nis's 1st concert, Day 2, Drawn to Dawn!
I am Takanashi Kiara and next to me is... Waaah!
Good morning, afternoon, evening, everyone!
This is Nijisanji!
That's right, it is finally time to start Day 2!
That's right, it's finally time to start Day 2!
Are you guys hyped? Yes!
Alright, before we kick things off, of course we have some important
safety rules and house guidelines to go over.
First, photography and the use of recording equipment are strictly prohibited during the performance.
First, photography and recording equipment are strictly prohibited during the performance.
However, if you are watching from home, screenshots are allowed, please take lots of screenshots.
However, if you're watching from home, screenshots are allowed, so please take lots of them.
Uh, yeah, screenshot ok desu yo.
Uh, yeah, screenshots are okay.
Also, the venue is smoke-free, so please refrain from smoking inside.
Unless you're smoking hot like me.
If you start feeling unwell at any point, unfeeling well, unfeeling well?
If you start feeling unwell at any point, please don't push yourself, just reach out to the nearest staff member for help and drink water.
If you start feeling unwell at any point, please don't push yourself, just reach out to staff for help and drink water.
For everyone's safety, please avoid any dangerous or disruptive behavior.
This, once again, no matter how hyped it is, includes moshing, diving,
sitting on shoulders, jumping excessively, or throwing objects toward the stage, climbing onto the stage, intentionally blocking the aisles or rushing toward the front is also not allowed.
sitting on shoulders, jumping excessively, throwing objects at the stage, climbing on stage, blocking aisles, or rushing the front.
Please refrain from disruptive shouting, erratic lightstick movements, or any extreme motions
that might interfere with the experience of those around you. Be considerate.
that might interfere with those around you. Be considerate.
If you don't follow the instructions of our staff or the venue staff, you may be asked to leave the venue.
If you don't follow the instructions of our staff or venue staff, you may be asked to leave.
Yeah, please.
Please keep in mind that the venue, organizers, performers, and staff cannot be held responsible
for any accidents, equipment damage, or trouble caused to blablabla- caused by failing to follow instruction.
for any accidents, equipment damage, or trouble caused by failing to follow instructions.
So, you stumbled over the same words.
It's hard, okay?
I'm trying my best here.
I can't read.
Additionally, any costs for damage resulting from ignoring these rules will be the responsibility of the person involved.
Additionally, any costs for damage resulting from ignoring these rules will be the person's responsibility.
There are cameras in the venue for filming and photography today, and you might appear in the footage or photos.
There are cameras for filming and photography today, and you might appear in the footage or photos.
These may be used for promotional purposes later on, so please keep that in mind.
And finally, just like yesterday, the concert will be in two parts,
there's a part for Wawa and there's a part for me, so please look forward to the both of them!
there's a part for Wawa and a part for me, so please look forward to both!
Yeah!
And yeah, that is it for the rules.
Yuhuu! The show is about to begin, so get ready!
Woohoo! The show is about to begin, so get ready!
Have fun! Have fun! See you! Bye-bye!
Enlightened by the powers that be
The ruler of a world run on insanity
It’s clear to me they still can’t see
I’m just a normal girl
Empowered by the ancient one’s call
We’re gonna be punstoppable, we’re not a cult
Nonsensical and nautical
Adventures lie in wait!
Gimme a one eight!
Ichi! Hachi! Takodachi!
Ina ina ina ina ina
俺のイナの世界線 守るためにタコになろう！！
My Ina world line, let's become takos to protect it!!
(Oisho!!)
(Heave-ho!!)
Ichi! Hachi! Takodachi!
Ina ina ina ina ina
いいタコになりますように Insanityで踊りましょう！
May we be good takos, let's dance in insanity!
(Oisho!!)
(Heave-ho!!)
Think of all that you could be…
We’re talking evolution, leave it all to me!
Maybe just a touch of purple ink…
What ya think?
It’s a song you can’t ignore
The ancient ones are calling you to be so much more!
Just put your hand in mine and be reborn…
In a blink!
Tell me what those legs are for?
(俺のイナ運ぶためです！)
(To carry my Ina!)
You could use 6 more!
(感謝感謝！！ありがたい！！！)
(Much appreciated!! So grateful!!!)
We could all get matching ears!
(They aren’t really ears though… eh??)
Sleepy eyes to fight your fears!
(例えばイナいないの世界！！！)
(For example, a world without Ina!)
Alright, listen to my song, am I striking a chord with you?
Stringing you along, so don’t let me get bored of you!
Eighty million strong and we’ve still got some more to do
Everybody shout! World domination!!!
Can I bank on your emotion? Do I have you invested?
I don’t wanna hear you say that you’re not interested!
Your unwavering devotion isn’t all I’ve requested
Do you care? Are you aware that you’re my dearest creations?!
Oyaoya!
Oh my, oh my!
A cute little takodachi found its way here.
Experimentation might be necessary…
Takos…. We have to cook!!
(いいタコだちの作り方！)
(How to make a good takodachi!)
You know me the best
You know my worst, see me hurt, but you don't judge
That, right there, is the scariest feeling
Opening and closing up again
I've been hurt so I don't trust
Now here we are, staring at the ceiling
I've said those words before but it was a lie
And you deserve to hear them a thousand times
If all it is is eight letters
Why is it so hard to say?
Why am I in my own way?
Why do I pull you close
And then ask you for space?
If all it is is eight letters
Why is it so hard to say?
Isn't it amazing how
almost every line on our hands align
When your hand's in mine
It's like I'm whole again, isn't that a sign
I should speak my mind
I've said those words before but it was a lie
And you deserve to hear them a thousand times
If all it is is eight letters
Why is it so hard to say?
Why am I in my own way?
Why do I pull you close
And then ask you for space?
If all it is is eight letters
Why is it so hard to say?
奪った？ それなんのことかしら
Was it stolen? Whatever could you be meaning now?
知らんぷっで 今日を重ねるの
Feigning ignorance through another day again
誓った 他の誰でもない きみの前で
My solemn vow that I had given you alone
愛のない愛 表明
Where I declared this loveless love of mine in front of you
奪った？ それなんのことかしら
Was it stolen? Whatever could you be meaning now?
決まり文句 演じ切るまさに
Committing myself to this play with pre-set lines
寝抱って飼い込んだ想出は
We're clinging to our memories that were hard to form
絡み合って 情を増していくの
Merging together as our feelings grow
なんかんだ言うが ちょっと黙ってや
Talking and talking and going on, could you just shut up a bit?
もうどれもこれも嘘に見えて仕舞い込んだんだ
Cause everything is starting to seem like a lie already to me
どこにきみの逃げる場所が残っている？
Is there anywhere remaining that you can still escape to?
そう僕も悪できみも悪さ 理解してんだ
Sure, me too I'm evil and you too are evil, I understood that
踊りちゃってライアー
Dancing away, liar
膨らんじまったこの愛は
This love has swelled up like a balloon
針を刺して嘘に変えよう
With a prick, let's pop it, turn it into a lie
「好き」と言っちゃって
"I love you" ending it
染まっちまってライアー
Let it soak in, liar
薄まっちまったこの愛は
Our love has watered down and grown so thin
きみが全部飲み干してよ
You can just go ahead and drink up everything
どこに行ったって もう異常だよ
No matter where you run, it can't be undone
奪った？ それなんのことかしら
Was it stolen? Whatever could you be meaning now?
知らんぷっで 今日も重なるの
Feigning ignorance for another day again
隠した誰も触れないように
Hid it away, so it can't be touched by anyone
渇くダンス 炭酸のメロディー
A thirsty dance of carbonated melody
シラを切って何度間違えば
Meaning that you keep making mistakes once again
嵌まった底なんて無い沼に
Had fallen into this bottomless swamp without
溺れたって気付くのですか？
Yet having realized that you are sinking down
誰れも彼れもきみのことを嘲笑っている
Anyone, everyone is making fun of and laughing at you
もう僕もきみが嘘に見えて仕舞い込んだんだ
And even I cannot help seeing you for nothing else but a lie
だけどなぜかきみのことを想っている
Somehow, for some reason, even now I am still thinking of you
そう僕も悪できみも悪さ 理解してんだ
Sure, me too I'm evil and you too are evil, I understood that
踊りちゃってライアー
Danced already, liar
謝ったってもう遅いの
By now it's too late to apologize
すでに恋の共犯者さ
We are partners already in this crime of love
戻れなくたって
There's no turning back
染まっちまってライアー
Soaked already, liar
裏返っちまってきみになる
Turn me inside out, I'll be one more you
はじめまして罪と罰よ
Very nice to meet you two, crime and punishment
なにを言ったって もう異常だよ
No matter what you say, it is now too late
苦い今に耐えてる
With a bitter present to endure,
僕だけの解読の暗号
My very own decoding code,
冗談笑い飛ばしてよ
Laughing off the joke,
万月の金銀修業
Training under the full moon,
七つの海の奥深くに
Deep within the seven seas,
隠る密事も
Hidden secrets too,
零れ瞳を狙う
Targeting spilling eyes,
愚かのみあの石屑
Only foolish rubble,
裁きを主を
Judging the master,
骨に当たる黒い魂の群れ
A flock of black souls striking bones,
影の底でしのび寄るざまの渦巻で
Sneaking at the bottom of shadows in a swirling vortex,
鍵のとじた箱を
A locked box,
開け出したいわ 諦めたいわ
I want to open it, I want to give up,
悪夢の中から逃げ出せるのにまだ叫んでる
Even though I can escape from the nightmare, I'm still shouting,
欲望が燃えたら
Once desire burns out,
奪った? それなんのことかしら
Was it stolen? Whatever could you be meaning now?
包み自身を信じ込ませて縛り付けて
Committing myself to this play with pre-set lines
とて気付いた
So realized,
際の出口 永遠の夜の中
The exit of the edge, in the eternal night,
目を覚ましてあなたの悪から
Awaken from your evil,
霧の夢に眠る綿津見
Sleeping in the misty dream, the cotton-stiffened sight
器重がね朽む棺
The vessel's toll rings out, the hull splits open wide
割れて白く夢は紅に 染めてわらべうたは途絶え消えた
The white dream turns to crimson, staining the lullaby away
magic pages open wide, spilling secrets from inside
now the story stirs again, a tale that never ends
distant waves, they call to me
echoing a memory
melancholic and forlorn
nostalgia reborn
刻々と壊されて 誰も読めない手紙
now it is time to find myself
that frightened infant of the past
trapped in a deathly hold, lost and cold, you're waiting for me
a ray of hope can lead the way
let me sing for you every day
a melody unveiled, light prevails, breaking through the void
時の虚眠る我が罪 孤独わらべうたの律 抱いて
刻々と輪廻して
>
偶然と必然の
狭間を揺れる振り子
>
now it is time to tell myself
you will never be alone
all sorrow disappears, no more fear, you're safe from the storm
a ray of light pierces the night
i will always be by your side
all voices raised in prayer, everywhere, breaking through the dawn
abyssal hymn
霧の夢に眠る綿津見
where past and future intertwine, the ancient sleeps
遥か古の未来で
misty dreams hold a prophecy of truth
出会う
someday soon
そして夜は その冷たさを 溶かして手を伸ばした
もういいよ 遠くても 叶えたい 私は
この胸に 痛みを 抱きしめていたいのに
夢のキャンバスに 続ける意味は
この胸に 輝いている Story
そして夜は その冷たさを 溶かして手を伸ばした
もういいよ 遠くても 叶えたい 私は
この胸に 痛みを 抱きしめていたいのに
夢のキャンバスに 言葉で包んだ
夢のキャンバスに 拾いおこしてゆく
この胸に 今輝いて
強くなくてもいい 壊れかけてもいい
この心は 壊に羽ばたいて
響くように 振り返ってゆく 私へと
Are you guys enjoying the show so far?
You know, um I was really...
I want to talk about Taco Tako first because
yesterday I heard you guys sing along to this instrumental,
and I was like...
I feel bad for not singing on day one, but you know, I knew I was opening for, you know, day two,
I feel bad for not singing on day one, but I knew I was opening for day two,
so I couldn't have thought of a better song to open than Taco Tako.
Hope you guys had fun singing it! Thank you again!
And of course, I sang two of my Senpai songs, um, Senchou's Dead Man's Chest
and 2005's... Palette!
I specifically wanted to... choose...
their songs because, um, they're, you know, Senpais that I really look up to, and I always feel like
their songs because they're, you know, Senpais that I really look up to, and I always feel like
my journey here wouldn't have been possible if I didn't discover my Senpais many, many years ago.
And I always, you know, wanted to pay respect to the path they paved for us.
So, yeah, I hope you guys enjoyed it!
And, um, you know, I, of course, didn't really tell you guys specifically what penlight colors to use,
but I knew you guys would get my message 'cause we share a brain cell, right? Right?
And, so, well, um now going by the different setlist, 'cause we, you know, have different setlist for day one and day two,
And, so, well, now going by the different setlist 'cause we have different setlists for day one and day two,
so, uh, you know, going by the process of elimination, we have a couple of songs from my new EP— wait, who here bought my EP?!
so, you know, going by the process of elimination, we have a couple of songs from my new EP— wait, who here bought my EP?!
Thank you so much! I hope you were lucky to get an autograph.
I tried to sign as much as possible, but, you know, sometimes you can't be lucky.
But yeah, I want you guys to have even more fun than before today. I mean, you always have fun, so that's good. But, um, yeah!
Now, you know, sing along, have fun, and I always think that a live stage is where not only me performing is creating the performance,
but you guys as well. You really help... you know, help everyone with that special experience. So let's create an unforgettable memory together today, okay?!
but you guys as well. You really help everyone with that special experience. So let's create an unforgettable memory together today, okay?!
Anyways, um I would also like to shout out to those watching at home and at the live viewing in the cinema.
Hello! Hello to thee again!
And also, the lovely, lovely girls doing a watch along right now. Hi guys! Thank you ID, and everyone else doing the watch along. Thank you, thank you!
And also, the lovely, lovely girls doing a watch-along right now. Hi guys! Thank you ID, and everyone else doing the watch-along. Thank you!
Um, you know, um I'm always amazed by everyone's support, um, and, and really without the support of Hololive numbers as well,
Um, you know, I'm always amazed by everyone's support, and really, without the support of Hololive members as well,
like, I wouldn't have had the confidence to stand here today. Thank you! I love you!
And, of course, I would like to remind you guys about the hashtag for today's concert as well: #TacoToriFirstConcert as usual.
Post your thoughts about it, post the screenshots—no videos, no videos!
Post the screenshots and, you know, wawa and I, whenever we have time, we've been checking the hashtag.
And of course, after as well, I want to hear, um, what you guys thought about the live, so, yeah! Thank you, thank you!
And of course, after as well, I want to hear what you guys thought about the live, so, yeah! Thank you, thank you!
And, unlike yesterday, first MC means I unfortunately have to bid farewell to those watching the sneak peek on YouTube. I'm sorry!
But if you want to keep the party going, head to the streaming site via the description, the comment—I don't know where the comment is.
But I know that, uh, some of you guys won't get a chance to see my new outfit that I revealed yesterday, so, I thought, maybe...
But I know that some of you guys won't get a chance to see my new outfit that I revealed yesterday, so I thought, maybe...
maybe you guys can help me transition into the new costume here so that even those of you...
Oh, and YouTube, Chigami-san can see!
Alright, so I'm gonna count down from three and count down with me, okay?
And then we'll switch into the new outfit for you guys to see. Keh keh keh.
And then we'll switch into the new outfit for you guys to see. Heh heh heh.
Ready?
Ready? Give me a one if you're ready!
Alright, alright, alright.
Alright, here we go.
Three!
Two!
One!
Wah!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Alright, it's time to move on to the next song.
And I think this song also fits the starry stage perfectly.
Not, not that one yet, but... keh keh keh.
Not, not that one yet, but... heh heh heh.
But this one is from one of my favorite franchises, so I hope you guys listen.
Anyways, the song will fit the starry stage perfectly. Please give it a listen.
無料パートは以上でした。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.